chubbiesshorts.com 2017-02-10

# Privacy Policy

We enjoy many things, two in particular are crushing the weekend and protecting our customers’ privacy.  We appreciate you visiting our website, www.chubbiesshorts.com (the "Site") and Mobile App (the "App") owned and operated by Chubbies Inc., (“Chubbies,” “we,” “us,” or “our”).  Here at Chubbies we believe that you have a right to know what information we collect from you, this is the good ole U S of A after all.  We want you to understand our commitment to protecting your privacy.  We’ve created this Privacy Policy to let you know what to expect when you interact with us on the Site and App, as well as on our mobile application (together with the Site and App, the “Services”). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time and we will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. We recommend that you consult this policy regularly for any changes.

By using our Services, you agree to the use, disclosure and procedures this Privacy Policy describes. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to third party websites ("Third Party Services"), such as, but not limited to, Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest and Instagram, that we do not own or control, even if you access them through the Services. We try to work only with Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, but we cannot take responsibility for their practices, content, or privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access so that you know how they will use and share your information.

## What Information We Collect

Our primary goals in collecting information are to improve our Site, App, Services, features and content, and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site and App. The information we collect from you falls into two categories: personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) and non-personally identifiable information (“Non-Personal Information”).This Privacy Policy covers both types and will tell you how we might collect and use each.

Personal Information we may collect from you includes:

  * your name and email address
  * your credit card information (although we use a third party payment processor), billing address and shipping address
  * live chats and customer services phone calls

We may also collect some of the following Non-Personal Information from you:

  * the IP address of the computer you use to access our Services
  * the type of browser software you are using
  * the date and time you access our Services
  * the website address, if any, that linked you to our Site
  * search engine search terms and advertising clicks/actions
  * other non-personally identifiable traffic data

Cookies and Pixel Tags

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site and App, to better understand how you interact with the Site and App and to monitor aggregate usage by Chubbies Users and web traffic routing on the Site and App. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site, App and Service and then close your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site, App or all functionality of the Service.

Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to Chubbies and e-commerce companies generally. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your login information, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. Please do not call Chubbies Customer Experience, as they are unable to take orders over the phone. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission's website.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Chubbies Blog

Chubbies offers a publicly accessible blog at blog.chubbiesshorts.com (the "Blog"). Please note that any information you provide on the Blog, including, but not limited to, comments, may be read, collected and used by others who access the Blog. Also, if you choose to comment on any Blog post, the content of such comment, along with your name, email address and website URL will be publicly viewable via the Blog.

Third Party Services

Chubbies appreciates that our users are active in many different communities, both offline and online, and we like facilitating that wherever we can. Some parts of our Services can be linked up with other accounts you have, such as your Facebook, Pinterest, or Twitter. If you link to Third Party Services from our Services, we may collect some information about your use of the Third Party Service. We will only be able to collect the information if you've authorized the Third Party Service to provide us with that information or if you've made the information public. Additionally, if you mention us through your Third Party Services, we may collect information and content related to your comment that is publicly available. If you wish to limit the information available to us, you should be sure to manage the privacy settings of your Third Party Services. One thing we won't ever store is your Third Party Service password.

Aggregated Information and Non-Identifying Information

We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, payment processors, web analytics and improvement of the Site's features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Chubbies cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Chubbies or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

Business Transfers

Chubbies may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

Chubbies is very concerned with safeguarding your information, but no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Chubbies transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Our Policy Towards Children

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [info@chubbiesshorts.com](mailto:info@chubbiesshorts.com) with "Privacy" as the subject line of the email. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@chubbiesshorts.com](mailto:info@chubbiesshorts.com) with "Privacy" as the subject line.
